GAJENDER SHARMA

Delhi, Delhi 110062 | 09015518867 | gs6852@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Practiced troubleshooter with excellent diagnostics and repair abilities, strong attention to detail and methodical approach. Expert Software and support user. Boost system performance by thoroughly evaluating and correcting different hardware and software issues.

Skills

•	Linux Adminitrator and Linux support	os Ticket tool and troubleshooting problem

• Window 7,8,8.1,10 and support Mail configure and troubleshooting

Work History

IT Executive (Linux Admin)

11/2019 to Current

Vinove Software And Service Pvt Ltd – Gurgaon, DELHI

- Installation ubuntu and other flavour
- Configure mysql ,sql lite db mongo, Robo3t etc
- Webservices Apache install, configure and troubleshooting etc
- Internet issue and troulbeshooting etc
- Pfsense install and configure for firewall

IT Executive 01/2018 to 11/2019

Multiarise Tech Solution Llp – Gurgaon, Haryana

- Service based company and client site project (from client site project i am going to OMAN)
- Working at window 7,8,10 install and troubleshooting etc
- Tally working server and troubleshooting
- Outlook configure pop and imap, make Archive, backup and troubleshooting etc
- Working at linux Linux flavours like Ubuntu ,fedora etc
- Installation ubuntu make server like samba install etc
- Software install and take backup like synkron etc
- Router ,switch configure ,access point configure and firewall
- · Openvpn,LAMP,mysql,sql and apache2 installation and configure

Desktop Support Engineer

05/2017 to 01/2018

Shambhu Shree Services Pvt – NEW DELHI, DELHI

- Collaborated with vendors to locate replacement components and resolve advanced problems.
- Services provide company networking and supporting program
- Tally issue and backup fixed
- · Backup and restore data
- Window 7,8,10 and ubuntu installation
- · Troubleshooting and support to user
- · Networking issue
- · System issue and software issue fixed it
- · Mail issue fixed configure and backup in outlook

Desktop Support Engineer

04/2016 to 03/2017

Simmtronic Infotech Pvt. Ltd – NEW DELHI, delhi

- Collaborated with vendors to locate replacement components and resolve advanced problems.
- Window installation 7,8,8.1 and 10 and troubleshooting problem
- Internet issue and network issue fixed it
- Desktop and laptop issue and software fixed it
- · Any software issue and installation fixed it
- · Any software crack and purchase support him

Education

10th: Science

2009

V.C .S.G.S.B.V.S.S.S - Delhi

• 58%

12th: Science

2011

DC Arya Senior Secondary School - Delhi

- Minored in [Science]
- 55%

B.TECH: Computer Science

2015

S.R.U University

• Graduated IN 69%